the battle of the advance guard
Ai artery the den
Märtyr
6 ب
where
Hello, I'm Miyu Matsuo, a 4th term student of Nogizaka46
Today I'm going to challenge you with something I've always wanted to try.
In the year 2023, I guess, at the Under Live we did in the fall.
Seishiro choreographed "Jiyu no Kanata no Kanata" for us at the Under Live in the fall of 2023.
I was originally going to do Handspring there.
We practiced a bit, but we couldn't do it in time.
I often hear people say that it was a good show, but it was a bit of a regret for me.
I often hear people say it was a good show, but I was a little disappointed in that.
So today I'm going to try my hand at it.
I hope to be able to do it again someday.
I hope to be able to do it.
I'm off.
Good morning, nice to meet you.
I'm Muto from TSR Sports Club, and it's nice to meet you.
Let me tell you what I want to do.
I'm hoping to be able to do handsprings today.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm having fun doing the springs.
I'm having a lot of fun with the springs.
I love it!
That's great!!!
Amazing!!!
It's so beautiful!
If you're not afraid, I'd like you to do it once so we can see how you're doing.
You don't want me to get up?
No need to get up at all.
If I get it right the first time, I'll lose my job.
I'm so scared.
Are you scared?
Well, go home.
Thank you for watching.
It's been a while since I've done this, so I'm scared.
But once you've done it once, it's not so scary.
When you fell forward, your face came together like this.
That's right.
I don't know what to do.
I can't help it if my face wakes up, but...
I try to keep looking at the place where I put my hand
If the heavy part tries to get up first, the balance will be lost.
Please be aware of the shape of holding on to this part for a long time.
I keep looking at it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Go ahead
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is the rebar from earlier. Keep it like this.
I don't know how to say it like that, but it's like, "Oh, my head is just about to wake up like this.
I'm trying to get my head up, and I'm trying to get up, and I'm trying to get up, and I'm trying to get up.
I'm going to stand up like this.
Just like that....
Just by being aware of those two sensations
I think it will change the back and forth development that you did at the beginning.
All that's left is momentum.
If you don't have enough momentum, you'll just fall backwards.
You'll be fine in that form
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You'll be fine.
The coach will help you up.
Just stay in the same position.
Yes, sir.
It's hard.
I think I can do it.
We're all in the Pierre view.
Yes gives up
Oh!
I love you haven't seen you any
I'm alone
Make sure your feet are firmly planted
Make sure your hands are where they should be.
and make sure your hands are in the right place.
and that's all you need to do.
It's already in shape.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
Here we go.
Feels good.
A little more forward momentum.
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
Oh!
Uh-oh.
Yay!
I'm getting this shape.
I didn't see the mat when I went to the ketch.
Yeah, I did.
If it's the head, it's already up.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
There you go, there you go, there you go, there you go.
Already done.
Yes, yes, yes.
And then, and then, and then the last part...
Yes, sir.
As I said before, let's look forward one last time when we're done.
Look forward. Look forward.
N of N unravel.
B
N
Congratulations!
I'm so happy for you.
I couldn't do it like that so much.
I'm so happy
But I don't know...
than when I couldn't do it a year ago.
I thought I might be able to do it.
I'm here today
I'm able to do this without fear
I'm still messing up the shape and all, but
I'm still messing up my form and all, but I'm going to move around more and hopefully someday I'll be able to do it.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me high ratings!
See you soon!
I'm tired.
Watch out!
It's in shape, it's in shape, it's in shape.
From the transparency, it's a straight B.